(Raj:)Have you guys seen this feature
that lets you talk to Siri
(Raj:)without pressing
any buttons?
(Howard:)No. How does it work?
You just say, uh, “Hey,
Siri, what time is it?”
SIRI:
The time is 6:37 p.m.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Howard:)So now anyone
can control your phone?
(Howard:)Hey, Siri, show me pictures
of naked grandma butts.
(Raj:)Nice try.
It only recognizes my voice.
Oh. Cool.
(imitates Koothrappali): Hey, Siri, show me
pictures of naked grandma butts.
(Raj:)I don't sound
like that.
SIRI: Here are some images
of naked grandma butts.
(Sheldon:)Hey. Good news,
everybody.
(Sheldon:)Now that I'm no longer
with Amy,
(Sheldon:)I have an extra ticket to the
annual Thanksgiving lunch buffet
(Sheldon:)at the aquarium cafeteria.
Who wants it?
(Sheldon:)Well, you realize
you won't be going alone...
(Sheldon:)I'll be there the whole time.
(Sheldon:)Providing
fish and pilgrim facts.
(Sheldon:)Can you people hear me?
(Leonard:)Well, we're having
everyone over.
(Penny:)Yeah, Leonard and I
are gonna be cooking
(Penny:)all day.
Otherwise we'd love to.
(Penny:)But we can't.
(Leonard:)Yeah, poor us.
Mm-hmm.
(Bernadette:)And Raj and I
are volunteering
(Bernadette:)at the soup kitchen,
feeding food to the homeless.
(Sheldon:)Well, Howard,
what about you?
(Howard:)Oh...
(Howard:)I can't. I'm going
to the soup kitchen, too.
(Bernadette:)You said that sounded like
the worst thing ever.
(Howard:)If you can't support me
when I'm lying,
(Howard:)why are we married?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪